Vahagn Ghaldunts

YEREVAN, ARMENIA | (374) 98 998 336

vahagnghaldunts07@gmail.com | Portfolio-Website | Github | Linkedin | Medium

PROFILE

I'm a Frontend Web Developer with a unique combination of skills and experience. My expertise in languages such as JavaScript, React.js, HTML, and CSS allows me to deliver quality work on a range of projects. I value collaboration, diversity, and innovation, and I enjoy working with and learning from different people and perspectives. I believe that I can bring my experience, and enthusiasm to any team or project I join.

EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL LEAD, PICSART ACADEMY - JAN 2024 - MAY 2024

Moviato is an innovative movie suggestion platform designed to transform the way users discover and enjoy films. Find further information here.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER, PICSART ACADEMY - NOV 2023 - JAN 2024

During my involvement in the development of the Academy-platform software, I adeptly applied my expertise in TypeScript, React.JS technologies. This project provided an opportunity to leverage my skills in frontend development to create a robust and user-friendly platform.

PRACTICE LEAD, PICSART ACADEMY/CODE REPUBLIC LAB - OCT 2023 - JAN 2024

As a JavaScript Practice Lead, my primary role is to actively support students in mastering the effective use of JavaScript skills. I facilitate interactive exercises to help participants deepen their understanding of JavaScript concepts, enhance problem-solving abilities, and gain valuable real-world programming experience.

EDUCATION

Picsart Academy, Yerevan, Armenia - Computer Science, 2022 - 2023

Goris State University, Goris, Armenia - Faculty of Computing and Automated Systems Software, 2022 - present

Yerevan State Medical University, Yerevan, Armenia - Faculty of General Medicine, 2018 - 2019

SKILLS

- JavaScript / Core JS
- > React.JS
- > TypeScript
- ➤ HTML5
- ➤ CSS3
- > OOAD
 - o SOLID Principles
 - o Design Patterns
 - o UML
- > Linux
- MongoDB (Familiarity)
- > Computer Architecture
- > Computer Networking
- > Asana
- > Git Version Control System
- > Visual Studio Code

PROJECTS

Moviato - Movie Suggestion Platform | Link

Moviato revolutionizes the film discovery process with its innovative platform, offering users a new and delightful way to explore and appreciate movies.

Flappy-Bird-Game | Link

Flappy Bird is an engaging arcade-style game where players control Faby, navigating through randomly generated pairs of pipes with equally sized gaps.

World-of-Flowers-Hangman-Armenian | Link

In World of Flowers Hangman, players guess a hidden flower name before the stick figure is hung. The game ends when they guess the name or run out of guesses.

Armenian - Native

English - Intermediate

Russian - Intermediate